Kenan Bölükbaşı

Keran Davidov

Software Engineer, Game Developer & Designer, Architect

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Software Engineer with in-depth knowledge in 3D scene description, surface representation and processing. Highly experienced in compiled languages, and low-level debugging. Highly experienced in project pipeline and tools development. Experienced in project management.

Previously: Game developer, and designer, Blender 3D specialist, Blender Foundation Certified Trainer.

PERSONAL DETAILS

CITIZENSHIP EU (Bulgarian), Turkish

DRIVER'S LICENCE B Class

EDUCATION

2005 - 2017 **Architecture (B.Arch.)**

Istanbul Technical University, ITU School of

Architecture, İstanbul

2001 - 2005 High School (Science and Math)

Nilüfer Milli Piyango Anatolian High School,

Bursa

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

ENGLISH Mastery (CEFR: C2)
TURKISH Native Speaker

HIGHLIGHTS

FILM CREDITS

2019 Avengers: Endgame

Weta Digital - Technology and Research

CONFERENCE TALKS & WORKSHOPS

2014 **Prototyping & Optimizing Game Asset Workflow**Blender Conference, Amsterdam

2014 Automated Sprite Rendering System in Blender Libre Graphics Meeting, Leipzig

2014 Blender Python Programming Workshop BlendFX Studios, Leipziq

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

2021 **NOP Mode**

A code annotation and navigation system.

2017 Twiniwt Mobile Game, 6x13 Games

Innovative symmetrical movement puzzle. Featured on AppStore & Play Store Indie Highlights. C++.

2016 **1FPS Retro Game Series, 6x13 Games** 4 mobile arcade games. C++.

2015 **Fossicker, The Asset Prospector, 6x13 Games** Designer & Programmer, Development Tool

WORK EXPERIENCE

UNITY

MAR 2022 - [CONT'D]

Software Engineer

WELLINGTON

Software Engineer at Weta Digital - Pipeline Department.

WETA DIGITAL | WĒTĀ FX

Jan 2018 - Mar 2022

Software Engineer

WELLINGTON

Software Engineer at Pipeline Department.

- Development and integration of various technologies for visual effects pipelines.
- Development of visual effects artist focused tools, developer focused tools and software libraries.

6x13 GAMES

JAN 2015 - DEC 2017

Founder, Project Leader & Developer

İSTANBUL

Project leader. Game design and development. Graphic design and game asset creation. Prototyping, pipeline optimization.

- Game design, game & level editor development, project lead, graphics and user interface design of TWINIWT, the innovative, free to play symmetrical movement puzzle.
 Globally featured on both AppStore and Play Store.
- Project management & development of 1FPS GAME SERIES.
 4 mobile F2P games: 1FPS: INVADERS, 1FPS: VACUUM,
 1FPS: FASTFOOD, 1FPS: GRAFFIT[WIP]
- Cocos2d-x based in-house cross-platform game framework.
- Design, development and artwork of WRECKJUMPER[WIP], forced-perspective sci-fi TBS with dynamic puzzle elements.
- Visualization module for an architectural research project (for evolutionary-algoritm driven facade generation) at ITU.
- Development of FOSSICKER, open source asset prospector.

EKSERIYA STUDIOS

Aug 2013 - Jan 2015

Graphics Department Lead & TD

İSTANBU

Decision making on graphics technology and workflow. Tools and pipeline development. Prototyping. Asset shading, lighting.

- Asset pipeline automation system (import, lighting, rendering, compositing & atlas) for mobile RTS, SILICON WARS.
- Environment art and map editor for RIOT DEFENSE game.

SOFTWARE SKILLS

[♥ Use | ⟨⟩ Modify | ► Teach]

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

₽₽₽₽₽ ⟨> **₽** C / C++

 PROPRIE
 ⟨⟨⟩⟩
 Common Lisp, Scheme

 PROPRIE
 ⟨⟨⟩⟩
 Python, UNIX Shell

DEVELOPMENT TOOLS & LIBRARIES

PPPP

Visual Studio

Compilers & Debuggers

One of the control System

One of the control System

GRAPHICS SOFTWARE

OPOPP () PUSD

GIMP, **Inkscape**, ImageMagick

📦 😭 💎 🥟 Maya, Houdini